Growth is a horror, science fiction, thriller film directed by Gabriel Cowan.
In 1989, a breakthrough in "advanced parasitic research" on
Cuttyhunk Island gave scientists a jump in human evolution.
Initial tests proved promising, as subjects experienced
heightened physical and mental strength and awareness.
But - something in the experiment went horribly wrong, and the island
mysteriously lost three quarters of its population.
Jamie Ackerman, played by Mircea Monroe.
Justin Roberts, played by Christopher Shand.
Marco, played by Brian Krause.
Kirstin Daniels, played by Nora Kirkpatrick.
Larkin Holberman, played by Richard Riehle.
Dr. Macavire, played by Lou Richards.
Growth is a 2010 American horror film written and directed by Gabriel Cowan.
The film explores themes of island, experiment, outbreak.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.